

Zeyu Eaton<sup>· 3rd</sup>

**Direct Part Production** 

Seattle University

Facilities Manager at Direct Part Production

E Spring St, Seattle, United states Contact info

200+ connections

Message

More

#### **Featured**



#### **Our New HP MJF**

Directpartsolution.com

Always one step ahead we provide the best for our customer so what new for you?

#### **About**

I have worked in the manufacturing industry for more than 12 years in a variety of roles but have found my true passion in facility's management.

As well as the smooth day-to-day running of the facility, I keep a tight watch on budgetary responsibilities and duties around optimizing operational efficiency. Since joining Direct Part Production I have been involved in ongoing site planning and implementing the facility infrastructure and utility systems.

Strong and assured on:

- Review and monitoring of current processes to optimize efficiency
- Scheduling of routine maintenance
- Troubleshooting any issues with the plant utility systems
- Writing of internal SOPs for relevant areas
- Analysis of potential improvements
- Design of new processes or procedures across the facility
- Oversight of improvement or installation projects
- Responsibility to ensure plant utility systems meet internal standards and external regulatory requirements

In my spare time, I enjoy meeting up with my friends and family, and I currently volunteer as a guest columnist for my local paper, The Daily Herald. I also enjoy reading business and economics magazines















Try Premium for

## **Activity**

213 followers

Zeyu Eaton commented on this post • 2h

Yes, I agree



3 comments

Zeyu Eaton commented on this post • 8h

Always with pleasure 🙏 Cristi! Looking forward to your continued success. #teamworkmakesthedreamwork

# **Experience**



Part Quality Engineer **Direct Part Production** 

May 2000 - Present Stamford, Connecticut, United States



Part Quality Engineer Phase 1 Coolants

May 2000 - May 2000 Seattle, United States

### **Education**



**Seattle University** 

Master of Business Administration (MBA), International Business 1999 - 2000



**City University of Seattle** 

BSBA (Bachelor of Science in Business Administration), Business Administration 1995 - 1998

#### Licenses & certifications



Certified SAFe® 5 Product Owner/Product Manager

Scaled Agile, Inc.

Issued May 2021 · No Expiration Date

Show credential 🗗

# Languages

## **English**

Native or bilingual proficiency